Class of 1945 Records, 1941-[ongoing]
Smith College Archives
Class of 1945 Records
1941-[ongoing]
Smith College. Class of 1945.
RG 80 UUID:190251c2-bbf6-4b62-9867-66e0e5bc1a1a
6 boxes (2.9 linear ft.)
Smith College Archives Northampton, MA
This collection contains photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, and other memorabilia from the commencement and reunions of the Class of 1945.
The Class of 1945 was the sixty-seventh graduating class of Smith College. As part of an accelerated war-time program, 100 students of the Class of 1945 graduated in August, 1944.
The Class of 1945 Records contain materials describing the history and activities of the Class of 1945, including materials from commencement, reunions, and other important events. Types of materials include photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, programs, letters, memory books, and other memorabilia.
Individual biographical files are also available, and often include photographs, photo albums, newspaper clippings, letters and correspondences, and class notes.
Information on Use
Terms of Access and Use
The records are open for research according to the regulations of the Smith College Archives without any additional restrictions.
History of the Collection
The Class of 1945 Records were created by the students and donated to the College Archives.
- Commencement 1945 (Box 2151, Folder 1)
- Commencement-August 1944 (Box 2151, Folder 2)
- Commencement-Photographs 1945 (Box 2151, Folder 3)
- Commencement-Speaker 1945 (Box 2151, Folder 4)
- Freshman Dance 1941 (Box 2151, Folder 5)
- Freshman Handbook 1941-1942 (Box 2151, Folder 6)
- General 1945 (Box 2151, Folder 7)
- Groups 1941-1945 (Box 2151, Folder 8)
- Hoop Rolling 1945 (Box 2151, Folder 9)
- Ivy Day 1945 (Box 2151, Folder 10)
- Ivy Day-Photographs 1945 (Box 2151, Folder 11)
- Class Letters 1967-2003 (Box 2151, Folder 12)
- Mountain Day 1942 (Box 2151, Folder 13)
- Officers 1941 (Box 2151, Folder 14)
- Reunions 1946 (Box 2151, Folder 15)
- Reunions 1954 (Box 2151, Folder 16)
- Reunions 1965 (Box 2151, Folder 17)
- Reunions 1970 (Box 2151, Folder 18)
- Reunions-Photographs 1970 (Box 2151, Folder 19)
- Reunions 1975-1980 (Box 2151, Folder 20)
- Reunions 1995 (Box 2151, Folder 21)
- Reunions 2000 (Box 2151, Folder 22)
- Reunions-Wartime Questionnaire 2000 (Box 2151, Folder 23)
- Songs 1945, n.d. (Box 2151, Folder 24)
- Sophomore Carnival 1943 (Box 2151, Folder 25)
- Class Supper 1945 (Box 2151, Folder 26)
- Reunion Book 1995 (Box 2152, Folder 1)
- 55th Reunion Newsletters 1995-2002 (Box 2152, Folder 2)
- Reunion Memories Book 1995 (Box 2152, Folder 3)
- Reunion Photographs 1995 (Box 2152, Folder 4)
- Reunions 2005 (Box 2152, Folder 5)